const Elections = [
	{
		questionText: 'Elections Part and Articles',
		ans: ['Part 15', 'A.324-A.329'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.325',
		ans: ['Can exlcude only on the basis of caste, religion, sex, race, and can even make sepratae list'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.324',
		ans: ['E.C.I shall contain C.E.C and othere as per parliament'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.326',
		ans: ['Universal Adult Franchise'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.327',
		ans: ['Parliament can make rules on elections of Central and State'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.328',
		ans: ['State can make Rules for elections in state, if parliament doesn\'t '],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'A.329',
		ans: ['Bar to Interference for Courts and Delimitations'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Disqualification of Registration in Electroler roll',
		ans: ['Section 16 ROP Act 1950'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Right to vote ',
		ans: ['Section 62 of ROP Act 1951'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Disqualification of MPs and MLAs',
		ans: ['Section 8(1,2,3) of ROP Act 1951'],
	},

];

export default Elections;
